netrition.com 2019-05-06

# Privacy Statement for Netrition, Inc.

#### Privacy Statement for Netrition

Netrition, Inc. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following statements disclose our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website.

Netrition, Inc. does not sell, trade, rent, or give your personal information to others except what is necessary to process an order. 

We may use your IP address (a network identification number) to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. 

Our site uses Cookies to keep track of your shopping cart and user preferences. We also may use Cookies to deliver content specific to your interests.

Our site uses an ordering system for customers to request products. We collect visitor's contact information (like their name, address, phone number and email address) and payment information (like their credit card numbers). Contact information from the ordering system is used to send orders and - if you choose to join our email mailing list(s) - information about our company. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the Choice/Opt-Out section below. Payment information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services. 

Use of your information: In general, personal information you submit to us is used to provide the Services, to respond to requests that you make, or to aid us in serving you better. We will also use the information to contact you via e-mail, phone call, or text for (1) phone number verification, (2) enrollment/activation activities, (3) response to your request/inquiry, (4) encouraging or enabling your use of the Services including, but not limited to, specific features, (5) billing inquiries, (6) to provide users material updates related to the Services.

This site contains links to other sites. Netrition, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Our website integrates technologies of trusted advertising partners (third-party companies) that allow the recognition of your device and the collection of information about your browsing activity in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. In particular, these partners collect information about your activity on this website to:

  * Enable us to show advertisements for our products and/or services to you on third-party websites and apps.

Our partners may use non-cookie technologies on which browser settings that block cookies might have no effect. Your browser may not permit you to block such technologies. For this reason, please keep in mind that you can block the collection and use of information related to you by advertising companies for the purpose of serving interest based advertising by visiting the following platforms of self-regulatory programs of which those companies are members:

  * The [NAI's opt-out platform](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/)
  * The [EDAA's opt-out platform](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/)
  * The [DAA's opt-out platform](http://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2&lang=EN)

Our advertising partners include:

  * Criteo

##### Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) which is the industry-standard encryption scheme to scramble data so it can be transmitted securely to us. We perform periodic security scans of computer systems responsible for the processing of customer information.

##### Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving email from us from within emails sent from our mailing list. Each email contains a link to uniquely remove the recipient's email address from the mailing list.

##### Google Analytics

Netrition uses Google Analytics, Google Analytics for Display Advertising, and Google Analytics/Adwords Remarketing to market our site across the web. Google Analytics collects information anonymously and reports website trends without identifying individual visitors. Google Analytics uses its own cookie to track visitor interactions. As a website owner, Netrition can view a variety of reports about how visitors interact with our website so we can improve our website and how people find it. For Remarketing, a cookie is placed on your browser, and then a 3rd party reads these cookies and may serve an ad on a 3rd party site. More information on Google Analytics can be found at: [www.google.com/analytics](http://www.google.com/analytics), [www.google.com/privacy.html](http://www.google.com/privacy.html) and [www.google.com/analytics/tos.html](http://www.google.com/analytics/tos.html). You can choose to opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and Remarketing by going to [www.google.com/ads/preferences](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences). 

##### Correct/Update

To modify information previously provided, visit <https://service.netrition.com/myaccount.html>

##### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:

Customer Relations  
Netrition, Inc.  
25 Corporate Circle, Suite 118  
Albany, NY 12203  
Or contact us online
